{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Painting \u0026 Staining Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40365/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40365,"taskName":"Painting or Staining - Small Projects","taskDescription":"Paint or Stain Single Items","xmTaskDescriptor":"Painting \u0026 Staining Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":223,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Paint Room Staining window wall","textMessagingName":"Sm Painting Proj","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes both interior or exterior. Small projects like, trim, doors, floors, furniture, etc.\r\nPainters generally also handle all relevant prep work including washing, scraping, sanding, caulking, patching \u0026 priming. Note separate categories for whole room painting, faux finishes, textured paint, murals, electrostatic painting, refinishing furniture \u0026 popcorn finishes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Small interior or exterior projects like trim, furniture, doors etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Paint or Stain Single Items or Small Rooms.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Wood Staining \u0026 Painting \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Wood Paneling, Trim, Small Rooms","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":55,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Paint or Stain Small Projects","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Interior or Exterior Painting or Staining - Small Projects","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Painting \u0026 Staining Project","urlName":"Painting-or-Staining-Small-Projects","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Small Job Painters \u0026 Staining Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Wood Painting, Paneling, Trim","searchKeywords":"Paint,Room,Staining,window,wall,floors,wood,porch,stain,faux,exterior,deck,jobs,custom,brick,appliance,Woodstock,,paiter,trim,doors,bathtub,tile,cabinets,cabinet,interior,improvement,fireplace,fence,Painting,Small","emcCategoryOid":-12054,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":659,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40365/":{"taskOID":40365,"originalTaskOID":40365,"setID":659,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5069,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5073,"questionDisplayText":"Features to be painted/stained","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Check off each feature that will need to be painted/stained. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2317,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2332,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior siding","answerDisplayText":"Exterior siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2341,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2418,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fencing/Gate","answerDisplayText":"Fencing/Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3319,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3346,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Interior walls","answerDisplayText":"Interior walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3350,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interior wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Interior wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4568,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Paneling","answerDisplayText":"Paneling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5072,"questionDisplayText":"New color","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will the new color be:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5069,"questionDisplayText":"Type of project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6001,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stain","answerDisplayText":"Stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5073,"questionDisplayText":"Features to be painted/stained","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Check off each feature that will need to be painted/stained. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2317,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2332,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior siding","answerDisplayText":"Exterior siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2341,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2418,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fencing/Gate","answerDisplayText":"Fencing/Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3319,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3346,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Interior walls","answerDisplayText":"Interior walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3350,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interior wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Interior wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4568,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Paneling","answerDisplayText":"Paneling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2317,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Exterior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2332,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior siding","answerDisplayText":"Exterior siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2341,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Exterior wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2418,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fencing/Gate","answerDisplayText":"Fencing/Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3319,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Interior door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3346,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Interior walls","answerDisplayText":"Interior walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3350,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Interior wood trim","answerDisplayText":"Interior wood trim","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1288,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2471,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4568,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Paneling","answerDisplayText":"Paneling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5072,"questionDisplayText":"New color","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will the new color be:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Lighter than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Lighter than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1829,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Darker than existing color","answerDisplayText":"Darker than existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5465,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Same or similar to existing color","answerDisplayText":"Same or similar to existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4000,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Multiple colors","answerDisplayText":"Multiple colors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}